hello everyone in this video we are
going to give the visual proof of a + b
square let we draw a square with side
length a definitely the area of this
square is equal to a square and having a
rectangle with the side length A and
B its area is equal to AB we draw
another square with side length as B
then area of this square is equal to b
square and definitely this is is a
rectangle with side length A and B and
having area is equal to a so this
complete figure is a square with side
length as a + b and its area is equal to
a + b s which is equal to sum of these
four areas which are these one and after
simplification we have a + b sare is
equal to a s + 2 a + b² that is the
answer